(Leslie:)...and who better to slow things down with
than you?
(Leonard:)I'm flattered.
(Leonard:)So how do you suggest we proceed?
(Leslie:)Your place. We'll order Chinese.
You'll rent a movie, artsy but accessible.
(Leslie:)Then light petting, no coitus.
- Sounds fun.
- I'll leave the details up to you.
(Leslie:)I think it's better
if you assume the male role.
(Leonard:)Thank you, that's very thoughtful.
(Leslie:)Great.
(Leslie:)Call me.
Hey, great news.
My mom sent me my old Nintendo 64.
LEONARD:
Oh.
- Terrific.
- You know what this means, don't you?
(Sheldon:)Break out the Red Bull.
It's time to rock "Mario" old school.
- I kind of have other plans tonight.
- But it's Friday.
Friday's always vintage-game night.
Look, Mom included the memory card.
We can pick up right where I left off
in 1999 when I had pernicious anemia.